Ben: I’m near the hotel, I think…
Izzy: Hey! Look out!
This is a great camera!
Can I take a photo?
Are you on holiday?
Ben: No. I’m a student.
At the Tensquare School of Photography.
Andre: These are good too.
But these… are nothing special.
Izzy: How are you, Carla?
Carla: I’m good. And you?
Ben: Uh… are you two friends?
Izzy: Do you want to go out sometime?
Ben: Me?
Izzy: Call me.
What do you want to see?
Ben: I want to see the real London.
Listen, Izzy.
My photography class has a little show next week.
Do you want to come?
Andre: She’s very talented – in fact,
she was my best student.
And now she’s working as a bike courier.
Ben: Wow, these are… really professional.
Izzy: I want to be a photo editor.
I… sent in an application and I got an interview.
Pamela: Oh, hey, Izzy! Good luck!
Izzy: Thanks, Pamela.
Ben: Oh, uh…How did the interview go?
Izzy: I was amazing!
Ben: Of course you were.
Izzy: See you when you get back.